(Penny:)No, I know.
(Penny:)I know what you meant.
It's just this is only our first date.
(Leonard:)Okay. Sure. No problem.
(Leonard:)Why don't we just figure out
where we're going...
...and when we want to get there?
(Leonard:)And then rate of speed
equals distance over time.
(Leonard:)Solve for R.
(Penny:)Or we could just wing it.
(Leonard:)That might work too.
- Good night, Leonard.
- Good night.
(Raj:)He's coming. Screen saver.
(Howard:)Oh, hey, Leonard.
(Howard:)- How was your date?
- Bite me.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, how could you just sit there
and let them spy on me?
(Sheldon:)They were clever.
(Sheldon:)They exploited my complete lack of interest
in what you were doing.
(Howard:)You should thank us.
When future generations try to determine...
(Howard:)...why your relationship with Penny
crashed and burned...